Guide to the History 126 scrapbooks, Spring 2007,2007.
History 126 scrapbooks, Spring 2007
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
History 126 scrapbooks, Spring 2007, 2007.
37-5-3602
Cornell University.Dept. of History.
18 volumes.
Scrapbooks
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Annotated student scrapbooks, compiled by students in Professor Carol Kammen's History 126 course for Spring 2007, documenting the Cornell experience especially the freshman experience. Compilers include Ariana Almeida, Leslie Chae, Peter Franz, Lisa Han, Nicole Handy, Emma Herzog, Edward Kim, Jr., Jen Koh, Samantha Krotz, Sora Lee, Scott Marrett, Natalie McClain, Kaitlyn McKeown, Ryan McNamara, Kate Morris, Alyssa Padover, Leif Paulson, and Liz Peters.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Annotated student scrapbooks, compiled by students in Professor Carol Kammen's History 126 course for Spring 2007, documenting the Cornell experience especially the freshman experience. Compilers include Ariana Almeida, Leslie Chae, Peter Franz, Lisa Han, Nicole Handy, Emma Herzog, Edward Kim, Jr., Jen Koh, Samantha Krotz, Sora Lee, Scott Marrett, Natalie McClain, Kaitlyn McKeown, Ryan McNamara, Kate Morris, Alyssa Padover, Leif Paulson, and Liz Peters.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Almeida, Arianna.; Chea, Leslie.; Franz, Peter.; Han, Lisa.; Handy, Nicole.; Herzog, Emma.; Kim, Edward,; Koh, Jen.; Krotz, Samantha.; Lee, Sora.; Marrett, Scott.; McClain, Natalie.; McKeown, Kaitlyn.; McNamara, Ryan.; Morris, Kate.; Padover, Alyssa.; Paulson, Leif.; Peters, Liz.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University; Cornell University.Class of 2010.
Subjects:
Women college students--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Form and Genre Terms:
Scrapbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Arianna Almeida, 2007 (Box 1)
- Emma Herzog, 2007 (Box 1)
- Natalie McClain, 2007 (Box 1)
- Kaitlyn McKeown, 2007 (Box 1)
- Alyssa Padover, 2007 (Box 1)
- Leif Paulson, 2007 (Box 1)
- Liz Peters, 2007 (Box 1)
- Leslie Chae, 2007 (Box 2)
- Peter Franz, 2007 (Box 2)
- Lisa Han, 2007 (Box 2)
- Nicole Handy, 2007 (Box 2)
- Edward C. Kim, Jr., 2007 (Box 2)
- Jen Koh, 2007 (Box 2)
- Samantha Krotz, 2007 (Box 2)
- Sora Lee, 2007 (Box 2)
- Scott Marrett, 2007 (Box 2)
- Ryan McNamara, 2007 (Box 2)
- Kate Morris, 2007 (Box 2)